Register of the Antonina R. von Arnold Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- FAMILY FILE, 1890-1977
  - Arnold, Roman Apollonovich von (father)
    - Writings
      - "Iubilei gen. D. L. Khorvata," Zaria, 1928 April 29 (Folder 18: 3)
- SERGEY SCHERBAKOFF FILE, 1912-1967
  - Biographical file
    - Book (biography and catalog)
      - Draft, n.d. (Folder 18: 4)
      - Mock-up. (Folder 18: 5)
        Includes advertising matter
    - Clippings about or mentioning Scherbakoff (Folder 18: 6)
    - Contracts (Folder 18: 7)
    - Critical appraisals (Folder 18: 8)
    - Exhibition catalogs. (Folder 18: 9)
      Includes advertisements
    - Identity papers (Folder 18: 10)
    - Letters of recommendation for Scherbakoff (Folder 18: 11)
    - Miscellany. (Box-folder 19: 1)
      Includes samples of Scherbakoff's artwork
  - Correspondence
    - General, and, 1923-1963 undated (Folder 19: 2)
    - Relating to artistic exhibitions, 1927-1930 (Folder 19: 3)
  - Subject file - Frontinskaia, Tamara M. (first wife). (Folder 19: 4-10)
    Includes biographical matter, correspondence and miscellany relating to her medical education and career
  - Subject file - Frontinskaia, Tamara M. (Box-folder 20: 1-2)
  - Writing - "Flying Pony," translation into English of Konek-Gorbunok, n.d. (Folder 20: 3)
- SUBJECT FILE, 1968-1970 (Folder 20: 4)
  Community Children's Nursery, minutes of meetings
- PRINTED MATTER, 1930-1979 (Folder 20: 5-6)
  See also OVERSIZE FILE
  Brochures, clippings, leaflets, offprints, programs. Most of the material deals with art and social work, some offprints and other items were given to von Arnold by their authors and bear autographs.
- OVERSIZE FILE, and, 1919-1942 undated (Box 21)
  - Diplomas (Folder 21: 1)
  - Printed matter (Folder 21: 2)
  - Writings (Folder 21: 3)
- ARTWORK, n.d. (Box 22-23)
- PHOTOGRAPHS, 1800s-1980s (Box 23)
  - Oversize prints (Folder 23: 1)
  - Albums. (Box-folder 24: 1-5)
    Photographs primarily of von Arnold and Scherbakoff clans, as well as of the Harbin Dental College. One album includes photographs of Scherbakoff's artworks and exhibitions
  - Negatives (Folder 25: 1)
  - Prints
    - von Arnold family (Folder 25: 2)
    - Antonina Romanovna von Arnold (individually and together with other family members) (Folder 25: 3-4)
    - Boris Romanovich von Arnold (Folder 25: 5)
    - Ekaterina Khristoforovna von Arnold (Folder 25: 6)
    - Liubov' Romanovna von Arnold (Box-folder 26: 1)
    - Roman Apollonovich von Arnold (Folder 26: 2)
    - Scherbakoff, Sergey (Folder 26: 3)
    - Frontinskaia, Tamara (Folder 26: 4)
    - McGuire, Ignatius (Folder 26: 5)
    - House in San Francisco (Folder 26: 6)
    - "Shcherbakovka" (country residence) (Folder 26: 7)
    - Miscellaneous and unidentified places (Folder 26: 8)
    - Miscellaneous and unidentified people (Folder 26: 9)
  - Oversize album. (Box-folder 27: 1)
    Photographs of the von Arnold clan, Harbin, China, and miscellaneous individuals and places
- MEMORABILIA, n.d. (Box 27)
- FINANCIAL RECORDS, 1942-1988 (Box 28)